# Henry Imoh



Henryimoh2@gmail.com



08135335812



linkedin.com/in/henry-imoh-5472171a1



https://imohenry.netlify.app

### Summary

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a web developer and content writer, with 3+ years of professional experience in building web products, as well as writing various forms of content. I also possess in-depth experience in the utilization of SEO techniques in driving conversion rates and engagements. Also, I have years of professional experience in Data analysis, photography, and design.

### **Experience**



#### Web developer & Copywriter

Get2work

Aug 2020 - Oct 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Developed website using frontend web development technologies, including Html, CSS, javascript, and PHP.

Conducted functional testing over course of the web development cycle.

Collaborated with Company Content creator in developing content strategies to drive engagements.

Increased engagements and conversion rates by 30% by Utilizing SEO principles and google analytics.

## **Web Developer**

Shecooks.ng

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020 (10 months)

Translated design personnel's ideation into concrete

user interfaces.

Developed functional digital design concepts across

various platforms to strengthen company brand and

identity.

Oversaw back-end development using PHP to maintain

website integrity, security, and efficiency.

Utilized customer personas and SEO tactics in driving meal sales (45%).

#### **Education**



#### Imo State University

B.A, History and International Studies 2016 - 2020

#### Skills

content management • css • html • JavaScript • React.js • PHP • jQuery • Copywriting • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • SQL

#### **Honors & Awards**



# Ever Reliable diplomat - NAHISS IMSU

Jul 2020

An award of merit for diligence towards the department of history and international studies.